What the hell?
Who the fuck are you?
Come on, you son of a bitch.
You bastard!
Fuck.
Let's go.
Woo-jin. Let's call an ambulance.
Gun-woo, things could get serious.
A man is dying.
Hyeon-ju.
An old homeless man was injured badly,
so we called an ambulance.
What about Yang Jae-myeong?
He ran away.
Fuck! I told you not to interfere!
But he was badly hurt.
We had no choice.
You don't even know him.
Why did you interfere?
Yes, but--
What do we do?
I'll give her a call.
- What?
- Hyeon-ju. About this…
We are really sorry.
This was 100% our fault.
Where are you?
I want to go apologize in person.
Forget it. It's over.
Hyeon-ju, just give us
five minutes of your time, please?
I am not kidding around at all.
I'm really sorry about this.
Gun-woo also wants to apologize.
Please, give us five minutes.
Please.
Come to the bookstore.
Woo-jin.
To be honest, I don't get it.
What? Get what?
If we had done nothing,
that homeless old man could've died.
You saw it yourself.
I did.
We did the right thing,
so why do you have to apologize like that?
- Why do we have to apologize?
- This was our first time on the job.
Hyeon-ju wasn't here,
so it's hard for her to understand.
We still don't know each other well,
and this happened.
If we apologize for things
that might cause misunderstandings,
I think we'll be able to communicate.
- But…
- Gun-woo.
I don't think you did anything wrong.
But for the sake of the job,
we should be able to smooth this out
if we help each other a bit.
Just this once, okay?
Yes, okay.
BLOODHOUNDS
Don't sit. This will be quick.
Did you fight Yang Jae-myeong?
It was unavoidable.
We can't work together.
What?
Isn't it obvious?
We gave you a sincere apology.
I don't need an apology!
Yang Jae-myeong saw your faces, didn't he?
My plan was to tail him
and gather evidence quietly.
Now that Yang Jae-myeong knows
someone is on his tail, he'll lie low.
Therefore, my plan is ruined.
We wore caps and masks.
He couldn't have seen our faces.
Right. Since you covered your face,
there's no way he'd recognize you.
Since this shitty hair was covered,
he wouldn't recognize you!
Fuck! I'd recognize you from a mile away!
What are you doing? Get out.
- We apologized.
- I said get out!
- We had no choice.
- How so?
It's our first time working together.
- We're not perfect!
- That's why I refused you!
We acted accordingly!
- According to what?
- I told you earlier!
You don't fucking get it!
Why did you bring up my hair?
- We'll leave.
- Fuck.
So stop screaming, please.
I'll find a way to return
the money Mr. Choi gave me.
Since Woo-jin and I listened
to your yelling,
please listen to me too.
If someone offered
to make your work go smoothly
in exchange for killing someone,
could you do it?
The Smile Capital boss
cut my face with a knife.
If I had done nothing
while a man was dying in front of me,
I'd be worse than that guy.
It would be wrong.
Think about it.
I'll find some other place.
Don't worry too much.
I'm sorry. I couldn't hold back.
You held back better than I did.
Are you hungry? Let's go
to this hangover soup place I know.
Wait a second.
It's probably closed
because of COVID. It's past ten.
That just made me more hungry.
I forgot.
My stomach hurts.
It's not my fault they're closed
because of COVID.
It's your fault for bringing it up.
You couldn't hold yourself back
with Hyeon-ju just now!
You said that I did a good job.
I said that
because you were moping like a loser.
I wasn't moping like a loser.
"I wasn't moping like a loser."
What are you doing?
I'm imitating you, you loser.
"Man, I'm hungry."
- "My stomach hurts."
- Wow.
You're so ugly.
How could you joke like that?
What? I wasn't joking. I'm being serious.
I'm seriously hurt by this, so apologize.
SORRY, I WAS WRONG. SEE YOU AT THE OFFICE
TOMORROW AT 10:00 A.M.
Woo-jin.
I knew we'd get through to her!
Hey, it's short!
- Short.
- Short!
You're so damn loud!
Don't get mad. It's just a game.
- That's expensive.
- Why so mad?
- Hurry up and go.
- God, I will!
It's your turn.
YANG JAE-MYEONG
I'M WAITING IN FRONT OF THE GOLF SHOP
- You have to wear your mask, sir.
- Got it.
What is it?
Someone is tailing us, sir.
Who was it?
They were young,
but they knew how to fight.
Are you sure?
- What?
- Are you sure someone's tailing you?
Focus.
The thing is…
Talk.
Before I started working for you,
I borrowed some money from a place.
They didn't mention wanting it back,
so I ignored the fuckers.
Get to the point.
But they came for the money recently.
The bastard that came to collect
was wearing a hat with a red cat on it.
The punk who got the jump on us today
was wearing the same hat.
Not a coincidence?
No. It was the same cap, sir.
Where did you borrow the money?
To explain yesterday's situation briefly,
Yang Jae-myeong had already robbed
that homeless man,
but he had forgotten about that.
So it resulted in a fight
when he started a conversation.
But how much money
do Jae-myeong's guys borrow
with one stolen ID?
About 50 million won per mule account.
That's 500 million for ten stolen IDs.
Jeez. How long have they been doing this?
At least for half a year, I think.
Wow! They must have made quite a fortune.
Did those loan sharks
just sit back and do nothing?
They'll be investigated by the cops
if they report it.
They're trying to recover the money
on their own but aren't able to.
This is my plan.
Find the private loan sharks
that Yang Jae-myeong conned
and recover the money
Yang Jae-myeong stole for a commission.
With a 1% commission,
that's three billion won.
We should charge 2%.
Woo-jin.
If loan sharks get conned,
wouldn't that make things worse
for the people who got loans from them?
What?
They'd have to harass their clients more
to recoup their losses.
So?
I just thought small businesses
would suffer the most.
You're right about that.
Yes.
How did they find us?
I don't know.
Turn off the lights and the sign outside.
Damn it!
PYEONGHWA BOOKS
- Turn your phones off.
- Okay.
Is it here? Are you sure?
Yes. I'm sure, sir.
You borrowed money from a bookstore?
Yes. The owner used to be
a big moneylender back in the day.
Hey, give this a kick.
Kick here.
Hurry up, you bastard.
- Kick harder.
- What?
Kick harder, you bastard!
Damn it.
Harder!
Kick harder, you bastard!
That's enough.
We'll need heavy equipment
to tear this down.
This here is the safe.
Last night on your way back,
did you check if you were being tailed?
Well, we took the bus.
They could have followed the bus.
If they had tailed us last night,
why didn't they jump us right away?
Why make their move now?
- He might've wanted to bring Kim Jun-min--
- Hyeon-ju.
Yang Jae-myeong saw
how we fought last night.
If he wanted to jump us,
he would've brought more people.
They probably weren't sure either.
But they might have caught on now.
Anyway, it's important to find out
how those people found us.
That's how we'll prevent
making the same mistake twice.
Okay. I totally understand.
Why don't we sit down for a chat? Yes?
Does Yang Jae-myeong know of this place?
He came here a long time ago.
That means he's caught onto
our connection with this place somehow.
Right.
Yes.
Well…
He could've recognized your cap, right?
The thing is,
I followed you a while back
when you were chasing down a homeless man.
Oh…
Yes, that was me.
The homeless man back then
was Yang Jae-myeong.
I see. Crap.
I was wearing
that cap back then, wasn't I?
Yes. Your hat left quite the impression.
Then that might've been
how they found out.
But why do you think
they kicked the shutters?
Our shutters were custom-made
with steel, not aluminum.
They were checking for that.
Damn, I think they'll be back.
Why is he here?
What were you guys doing?
That white car came here, didn't it?
Speak up.
I am sorry, sir. It's my fault.
We went out on a job last night.
What kind of job?
The thing is…
We were tailing Yang Jae-myeong.
Why?
Grandpa, loan sharks are desperate
to catch Yang Jae-myeong.
I'm sure they'll be willing to pay for it.
And I happen to be
the only one who can catch him.
Is this about money?
It's good to make money.
What did you guys do?
They are my bodyguards, aren't they?
I'm not hurt.
I'm disappointed in you.
I'm disappointed in you too, Grandpa.
It's clear Yang Jae-myeong is
up to no good.
Why aren't you doing anything?
Mr. Hwang could get rid of him
with a snap of his finger!
Are you frustrated?
I'm even more frustrated!
Gun-woo, take off that bandage.
- What?
- Hurry up and do it.
What? Okay.
If Yang Jae-myeong and Kim Jun-min
keep conning loan sharks,
they'll inevitably threaten
and tighten their grip
on powerless people like Gun-woo.
That would effectively render
all the charity work you do meaningless.
Your money will go straight
into their pockets!
If you really want to help those in need,
you should weed out the punks
like Yang Jae-myeong first.
Who did that to your face?
The Smile Capital boss did it, sir.
What's his name?
Well, I don't know his name.
He had a long knife scar
running down his left cheek.
Go back home.
Sir.
Could it just be a coincidence?
Please check if Kim Myeong-gil is
the CEO of Smile Capital.
Yes, sir.
Juju.
What?
You called us your bodyguards.
I have to say, that felt good.
So?
So I thought it might be nice
to talk casually.
We are a team, after all, Juju.
So, we're not a team
if we don't speak casually?
It's a suggestion because it'd be nice
if we could work as one big happy family.
If we're a family, the oldest
should treat the rest to a meal.
Are you buying?
I prefer sticking
to the formalities, ma'am.
I'm kidding.
Let's use Grandpa's credit card.
What do you want?
Rib eye.
Then you pay.
A barbecue buffet.
- A barbecue buffet?
- Yes. I know a great place.
Well, all right.
Let's go!
How long have you been friends
with Gun-woo?
I don't think it matters
how long you've known a person.
Knowing someone a long time
doesn't mean you're real friends.
So?
What really matters is
how similar your life trajectories are.
To be able to understand one another,
even after a short conversation.
That's important.
- And that's you two?
- Right.
Besides, boxers like us exchange more than
just our fists in an exchange of blows.
"So that's the kind of life you've lived."
Pow!
"This is how I've lived."
Each blow contains
the fighters' character,
heart, experience, hysteria…
History?
History.
We see it all. We know it all.
Sure.
Besides, Gun-woo is
a senior Marine.
And that tells you everything.
What exactly does it tell you?
Everything.
Everything about what?
Juju, this isn't something
that can be explained.
It's just a Marine thing.
It's like when rappers use hip-hop
as an all-encompassing term
when they look at something
and go, "This is hip-hop."
It's indescribable.
I see. Indescribable, you say?
- Are you mocking me?
- Of course not.
This stuff is really…
- Here.
- Right.
What?
You haven't even turned on the grill yet?
You never told me to.
It's customary for whoever is
at the table to turn on the grill.
I didn't know.
Why didn't you turn it on and go?
How could I? The grill would've burned
by the time I came back.
How would iron burn up?
It's not the iron that burns.
I'm saying that the meat will burn
if the grill is too hot.
So the meat will burn.
That's what "burning the grill" is.
That's what professional grillers say.
I'm just a civilian.
My mom says "burning the grill" too.
Well, my mom doesn't.
- For someone who knows meat--
- There!
Get grilling.
Well, I can't.
You can't put meat on a lukewarm grill.
Yes, that'll ruin the flavor.
You've got to wait.
Shall we talk while the grill heats up?
Gun-woo. Just speak naturally.
Right. Are you and Mr. Choi related?
What? That came out of left field.
I was actually curious about that too.
Well…
Long story short.
I was diagnosed with spinal cancer
when I was eight.
I was cured by the time I was ten,
but my dad passed away.
So I was sent to an orphanage,
but I hated it so much I ran away.
I used to get so hungry,
I ate leftover black bean sauce noodles
that people left on their doorsteps.
I also worked at bars
with other runaway kids,
but that was so hard.
So I went back to the orphanage.
I was dragged off to a different orphanage
when I was 17.
Grandpa was the owner there.
- Mr. Choi?
- Yes.
He built an orphanage
to do something meaningful.
He was really nice to me in particular.
At first, I thought he might be a pervert,
but I realized as time passed…
he was just being himself.
Grandpa let me learn everything I couldn't
because I didn't have the money.
I learned Kendo
and how to ride a motorcycle.
I can tell Mr. Choi is a nice person.
Since middle school,
I've worked part-time jobs with my mom
to pay off my dad's debt.
When our debt grew to 100 million won,
I felt utterly helpless.
I know how scary
a hundred million won can be.
So when Mr. Choi gave me that money,
telling me to pay off my debts,
I thought to myself
that I need to protect this man
at all costs.
Grandpa told me that in order
to judge someone's depth of character,
I should open up my mind.
People with depth of character will see
your earnestness and return it in kind,
and those who lack depth
will use that against you.
- That's true.
- You're a nice person, Gun-woo.
Right. I'm good at being nice
and being diligent.
- I think we can start grilling now.
- Sure.
Talk about perfect timing.
You're learning.
I learned from the best, right?
I suddenly feel left out.
Never mind. Hurry up and flip it.
I can't do that.
Trust him. He's good at this.
God, I can't get used to
this conversation.
Okay, take your time.
Smells amazing.
- Let's clean out the buffet today.
- Sure.
- When do you get the stitches out?
- Tomorrow.
Does it hurt?
Well, it's bearable.
- I asked for mine hot.
- It's better cold in the winter.
Jeez, seriously.
- Hyeon-ju.
- Yes.
Yang Jae-myeong knows our location.
Shouldn't we do something about it?
I'll talk it over with Grandpa.
- Ask quickly. We don't have time.
- Okay.
Ms. Lee.
The lobby is a hotel's first impression.
I want our international guests
to see the most Korean, beautiful,
and majestic lobby there is.
The kind of thing
they've never experienced before.
Yes, I understand.
TEAM LEADER LEE SO-HYEON
I look forward to hearing
your brilliant ideas
at the meeting tomorrow.
Our casino will be
on the top floor of that hotel.
My goal is 100 billion won
in annual revenue.
There are a lot of people
itching for a fix now that
gambling in Macau's been blocked off.
We'll book them a suite
every week to let them have fun.
We'll secretly catch them
gambling on camera.
Once we have enough cash,
Jang-do will hand over the evidence
of illegal gambling to the police.
When the hotel is ruined
and worth nothing,
we'll swoop in
and take over the whole thing.
Once Jang-do returns
with dirt on Director Hong,
we need to be ready to spend 100 billion.
We're currently
about 50 billion short, right?
Yes, sir.
It's time to collect on everything.
Sell off anything that's of any value.
Coming through!
Yes, sir.
That car you mentioned just came in.
Okay.
I'll be right back, sir.
What's going on?
CAR WASH EXIT
NO PARKING
Hello!
What's happening? Damn it.
Look at this guy.
- Keep them down.
- Damn it!
That's gross, man. Damn it.
What is this punk doing?
Spare me.
Grab him!
You're fucking dead, you son of a bitch.
Where are you going?
Hey, strip him down.
Hey, come here.
Hello, sir. Right this way.
- Is he in there right now?
- Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
- You can count it.
- Thank you, sir.
- You son of a bitch.
- Fuck.
I'm sorry.
Please give me something to wear.
You boys sure did a number on him.
- Hello, sir!
It's too cold.
Can you give me some clothes?
I'm sorry, sir.
Hi there.
You…
It's you, isn't it? Fuck.
Motherfucker.
You were acting like hot shit.
Prick.
You know,
you shouldn't have fucked around with him.
Did you think he'd get scared
and apologize to you or something
just because your cousin's a cop?
Let me teach you a valuable lesson.
Untamed animals bite back if you hit them.
It doesn't matter how much stronger
or weaker you are than them.
They just bite back.
Now then.
Strip down.
What?
Take off your underwear.
Okay, I get it now.
Please let me off just this once.
- Damn it.
- I'm sorry.
I don't know what it's about…
Hey, In-beom.
Let me off the hook just this once.
Let's wrap it up.
Do you want to strip or not?
Don't kill me.
- Please let me live.
- Drink some more.
Do you want to strip or not?
I'll strip down!
Right now.
Good call.
Director Hong, let's see you strip.
I GOT SOMETHING BIG
All right, that's enough.
KICKBOXING
Get it up. Come on.
Yes.
Mr. Choi, the Kim Myeong-gil we know
is indeed the CEO of Smile Capital.
I see.
I'm coming to pick you up.
I'll be there soon, sir.
Okay.
I'm sorry for the sudden decision.
Recently, I've gone through
personal difficulties.
It's been decided after much thought,
so I hope you'll understand.
Our company will close
at the end of this month.
I will be wiring you
a year's wages and your severance pay.
Thanks for everything.
Sir, what about
our money that's out there right now?
I'll take care of it.
Dad.
- Yes.
- This is Oh In-muk in security, sir.
I think robbers broke into your office.
How many?
I think there are two.
Hey!
You said ten minutes is enough.
This model normally comes
with a six-digit combination.
This one has eight.
I think they modified it.
- So what?
- I need more time.
Hurry it up.
I got it!
Okay. Get out of the way.
PRIVATE LOAN STANDARD AGREEMENT
These promissory notes
are worth a billion won each.
What happened?
No one has come out.
I've stopped the elevator.
I see.
Well, shall I accompany you?
No, that's fine. Thank you.
Wait. Let me just borrow this.
Sure.
Who are you?
How did you get in?
Who sent you?
Damn it.
Fuck.
Sir, are you okay?
Kill that bastard!
It's okay, Beom. Okay?
- Snap out of it, Beom.
- Okay.
- Yes?
- Yes, sir.
Kang In-beom!
We don't have time.
Take all the money in the safe
and head down first.
Pull yourself together.
Sir!
He's gone.
- Go down first.
- Yes, sir.
- Mr. Choi.
- Yes?
Have you given it some thought?
Come on. What's the issue here?
Let's avoid Yang Jae-myeong.
Why?
They kill people.
Let's also move the bookstore.
Why?
Hyeon-ju.
Look at me.
I am old and tired.
There's no strength or courage left in me
to fight them.
I want to live out
my remaining days in peace,
teaching you the things
I want to teach you
and giving you the things
I want to leave to you.
That is my only wish.
Can you help me with that?
Good.
Thank you.
The value of gold is bound to rise
whenever people lose confidence
in fiat currency.
That's why it's safest
to have your slush fund in gold.
If you melt gold
and mix it with other gold,
it practically launders itself.
That's the first thing
I learned from Choi.
Failing to get my hands
on his hidden gold…
I still regret it.
That old fuck.
Why did he have to close the damn company?
Beom.
Yes, sir.
Get in here.
What do you think?
It's amazing.
Each bar is worth 500 million.
If our business in Korea goes south,
you and I will take this
and go to Vietnam.
I planted someone
in the Vietnamese government.
With this,
we should be able to live like kings
for the rest of our days.
Thank you, sir.
You're my brother.
I would do anything for you.
Beom.
You're all I've got.
You know that, right?
Come on.
They have the best stir-fried pork
in the world.
- It's that good?
- Yes.
Auntie?
Auntie.
Yes, it's Woo-jin.
Oh God, Woo-jin.
What happened?
I took out a private loan.
They told me to pay them back.
I told them I didn't have money
because my business isn't doing well.
They smashed everything.
God, I'm scared.
What should I do?
She can't run her business
because you wrecked the place.
How do you expect her
to pay back your interest now?
She wasn't paying back.
I'm saying go easy.
Times are tough for everyone.
Then how am I supposed to make a living?
Why don't you pay for her?
You know I don't have the money for that.
Then just shut your mouth.
Mind your own business. Got it?
Fine.
It's Im.
He's a guy I used to work with.
He got conned recently
by someone he lent 500 million won to.
- Is it Yang Jae-myeong?
- I don't know.
I didn't ask for the details.
But it was a homeless person's ID
and a mule account.
Identical MO.
It is him.
We should catch him.
I'm a victim too. I just can't do nothing.
Grandpa told us to lie low.
They're dangerous people.
I think it's wrong to do nothing.
What if I call him back
and tell him about Yang
so he can catch him?
If the goal is to catch him,
we should do it.
We might make money.
If we make money from this,
can I use it to help Auntie?
We'll split it evenly.
Feel free to use it however you see fit.
- All right.
- Then I want to help her too.
Come over here.
Come on over.
Damn it.
Thank you.
All in.
Sir, you should take a look at this.
That car.
They turned off the engine,
but no one's getting out.
- Get ready.
- Yes, sir.
Hey, check your phone.
Yes, sir.
Sir, they're here.
Do exactly as I say in two hours.
They're here.
Let's go.
You're gonna die today, fuckers.
Yes, sir.
You can come down now.
Come on out!
I know you're there, so hurry up
and show yourselves, fuckers!
Come out, you son of a bitch!
Are you playing hide-and-seek?
Motherfuckers.
Please pick up…
HYEON-JU
- Yes?
- Grandpa.
The guys are in danger.
Where are you?
Run faster.
- Hey, go!
- Let's go!
You sons of bitches!
Go.
Fuck.
Go!
Fuck. This is insane.
Subtitle translation by: